One two Three!
Good morning!
I just want to say before we start:
I've been in a little bad mood today so ... damn lucky we are here now
I'll probably gasp up!
[Laugh]
[Laughs] Fy fuck!
[High-five sound] It's quiet.
Shall we say 'Gomorron'?
-Yes, Gomorron!
It is still sick, that it does not rain today.
-17 degrees!
What the hell!
[They scream]
Hell!
I thought we would spin around there?
Well, we can't hang up and down in a fucking strap.
Imagine if you had brought Sam and Love on this, they didn't have ...
They hadn't gone this!
- No!
He had been terrified!
Fun that everyone just looks at us ...
We just [talk nonsense]
... the parents could chill.
My mom always said so instead: "Please Jonas, don't swim after dinner because we want to chill a little"
[Uppetempo music]
So now we are at the water park and just as we left the hospital ...
... because you had problems.
Hanging purse.
Could not fix so can go with it anyway.
We get to present our experts too, you may say hello to the camera and what you are called.
Hello!
Adam.
-Tjena, Rickard.
They will take care of us today so we don't ... shit down.
They are experts.
-There is no one who dares to trust us.
The idea is today that we will test all these fun as well.
[In chorus] -aah.
After all, someone has made an emo-earth guy!
[Someone sings on the song in the background]
[Men's voice sings] "'Cause Tonight Will Be The Night That I Will Fall For You!"
From free fall, Skara Summerland and Rutch canoes to the motorhome and advertising for Air Up.
We've worked with these before,
And it's so amazing, for:
You buy one like this and you put a capsule on,
And then you drink, and then you are tricked via the scent capsule that the water tastes just that taste it stands.
And what is also great that this is the new bottle, such a metal bottle.
So it keeps cold very good.
So you pour cold water here it is cold for a long time.
Such a taste pod is five liters of water,
It smells creamy.
I'll test it so we'll see ...
Mmm, "Sweet Coconut", I recommend it.
And this is how it is: we have a code for you now,
It's JLC10, so you get ten (10%) percent discount.
So click on the link in the description,
Go in and treat yourself to a bottle.
Drink water!
You forget it.
You have to drink more water.
And the code is valid for fifth (5) September.
It cannot be combined with other offers ... so.
Go to the link in the description and see if something is right for you.
Listen to this then.
Back to the Rutch Canoes.
Who wants to go with Strawberry?
[Lucas] But you go together.